John W. Tukey Papers 1937-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.117
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Works By Tukey, 1938-1994; 25 linear feet
  - Subseries A. Papers, 14 linear feet
    Time series work within the series includes What Does the Mean-Square-Successive-Difference Measure When Applied to Time Series? (1950); The Spectral Representation and Transformation Properties with High Moments of Stationary Time Series (1953); Time Series Alanysis (Not Analysis) written with Bruce P. Bogert and M. J. R. Healy in 1962 and Can We Predict Where "Time Series" Should Go Next? (1978). There are several undated papers on time series with the Works Series as well.
    Tukey wrote on the topic of multiple comparisons for years; about half of his papers within this collection are collaborations. Multiple comparisons works written solely by Tukey include two folders labeled Multiple Comparisons (n.d.) containing 22 items; The Problem of Multiple Comparison (1973); and Some Thoughts on Multiple Comparisons 1992). Multiple comparison collaborations include: Short-Cut Multiple Comparisons for Balanced, Single and Double Classifications: Part 1, Results and Short-Cut Multiple Comparisons for Balanced, Single and Double Classifications: Part 2. Derivations and Approximations with T. E. Kurtz, R. F. Link, and D. L. Wallace; and Controlling Error in Multiple Comparisons, with Special Attention to the National Assessment of Educational Progress with Lyle Jones and Valerie S.L. Williams.
    "Data analysis," Tukey’s method for studying experimental results, was an important contribution to the field and can be credited with changing the standard and language of statistics. Tukey acknowledged two types of data analysis: exploratory data analysis and confirmatory data analysis. There are over a dozen papers within the collection on Exploratory Data Analysis between 1970 and 1994. (Several papers are undated and therefore could have been written before or after the recorded dates.) The earliest exploratory data analysis titles are Exploratory Data Analysis for Physicists and a folder containing 22 items labeled Comments on Exploratory Data Analysis Later papers on exploratory data analysis include: Exploratory Data Analysis, 1991-1994 (1993) and Exploratory Data Analysis, 1995-2005. There are two confirmatory data analysis papers with in the Series: We Need both Exploratory and Confirmatory and Some Illustrations of Confirmatory Analysis.
    Analysis of variance (ANOVA) and regression are the guiding principles behind statistics and Tukey made many important contributions to each of them. ANOVA papers include: Dyadic Anova, An Analysis of Variance for Vectors (1949), How to Look at ANOVA AND What it Can Do (1988) and Some Set-Ups for ANOVA-Like Inference (1990). There are papers on many other topics within the Works by Tukey Series; the mentioned titles are representative of just a small sample of relevant topics.
    - 0% Points for Pearson Curves, n.d.; 1 item; Kadane, Joseph B., Michael M. Meyer, and John W. Tukey
    - 13-Dimensional Forest, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - 1969-1970 Science: National Results and Illustrations of Group Comparisons, 1993; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - 1990 Census Coverage Evaluation Operations, 1991; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - 1n p/1-p Plots, 1980 September 17; 2 items; John W. Tukey
    - Accidentally Correct Weighting vs. Misweighting, 1981; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Accumulation Module, a Flexible Source of Summarized Values, The, 1990; 1 item; Tukey, John W, and Paul A. Tukey
    - Additional Prime Analysis of the HEI CO-angina Study, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Adjusting the 1980 Census of Population and Housing, 1989; 1 item; Ericksen, Eugene P., Joseph B. Kadane, and John w. Tukey
    - Adsorption and Desorption of Organic Compounds from Particles, 1985 December 19; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Albert Madansky, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Algorithm for the Machine Calculation of Complex Fourier Series, An, 1965; 1 item; Cooley, James W. and John W. Tukey
    - Allowances for Various Types of Error Rates, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Alphabet for Statistician's Expert Systems, An, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Alternate Guidance in Hyperstack Pursuit, 1981 November 23; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - An Immunological View of Robust Estimation, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - An Improved Mantel-Bryan Procedure for "Safety" Testing of Carcinogens, 1975 April; 1 item; Bohidar, Neeti R., Charles C. Brown, Joseph L. Ciminera, Nathan Mantel, and John W. Tukey
    - An Inequality for Deviations from Medians, 1946; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of a Class of Partially Balanced Designs (Diagonal Squares), 1952 May 20; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Covariance: A Review, 1956 September 7; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Data from a Randomized Block Design with Many Missing Observations, 1 item; Bohidar, Neeti R., Joseph L. Ciminera, Joseph F. Heyse and John W. Tukey
    - Analysis of Data, The, 1962; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Data: Exploration as One Road to Discovery, The, 1976 August 12; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Data: the Future with the Past, The, 1976 August 12; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Randomized Experiments, 1984 March 26; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Variance Computations, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Variance, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analysis of Variance: Preliminary Documentation, 1982 May 10; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Analyzing Data: Santification or Detective Work, 1969; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Another Beta-Function Approximation, 1949 November 23; 1 item; Scheffe, Henry and John W. Tukey
    - Another Comparison of Range and Standard Deviation, 1950 December 17; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Another Look at the Future, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Answer to Query 113, 1955; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Antiquadrature Formulas as Routes to Less Biased Estimates, 1957 May; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Antithesis or Regression, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Approach to U.S. Cancer Death Rates Involving Urbanization and Geographic Contiguity, An: 1. A Simple Adjustment for Urbanization, An, 1990 November 5; 1 item; Kafadar, Karen and John W. Tukey
    - Approaches to Analysis of Data that Concentrate near Intermediate-dimensional Manifolds, 1980; 1 item; Friedman, Jerome H., John W. Tukey and Paul A. Tukey
    - Approaches to Analysis of Data the Concentrate Near Higher-Dimensional Manifolds, 1979 August 1; 2 items; Friedman, Jerome H., John W. Tukey and Paul A. Tukey
    - Approaching Multivariate Control, n.d.; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Approaching the Prioritization of Complex Mixtures, 1989 December 20; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Approximate Behavior of the Distribution of Winsorized t (Trimming/Winsorizaion 2), 1968; 1 item; Dixon, W. J. and John W. Tukey
    - Approximate Confidence Limits for Estimates, n.d.; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Approximate Confidence Limits for Non-linear Estimates, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Approximate Formula for the Average Gaps in Gaussin Orders Statistics, An, 1967 June 4; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Approximate Means and Standard Deviations Based on Distances Betweem Percentage Point of Frequency Curves, 4 items; Pearson, E. S. and John w. Tukey
    - Approximate Operating Characteristics of Combined Variables and Attribute Sampling Plane, The, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Approximate Weights, 1948; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Approximation of the Distribution of the Product of Beta Variables by a Single Beta Variable, 1946 September 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W. and S. S. Wilks
    - Approximations to the Upper 5% points of Fisher's B Distribution and Non-central X2, 1957 December; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Argument at to Why Certain Lag Windows Always Give Non-negative Spectral Estimates, 1962 May 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Arms Control and Behavioral Science, 1959 November 4; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Asking Simple Questions, Naïve Downsweeping, 1988 October; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Assessing the Behavior of Robust Etimates of Location in Small Samples: Introduction to Configural Polysampling, 1981 March; 1 item; Pregibon, Daryl and John W. Tukey
    - Assessing the Information Contained in a Geological Contour Map, 1966 May; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Assessing the Tolerability of Error Distribution, with Special Attention to the Adjustment of the Census, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Assessiong the Core, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Assessment of Variation in not too Many Dimensions-- Comparable Sample Sizes for a Worst Case Gaussian Background, The, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Assessment of Various Structural Regression Coefficients, n.d.; 1 item; Gentleman, W. Morven and John W. Tukey
    - Asymptotic Characteristics of the Estimates, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Asymptotic Moments and Expectations, 1948 March 11; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Authors' Reply to Anscombe's Comments, 1965; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Automatic Selection of Thematic Excerpts for Summary Creation, 1994; 1 item; Chen, Francine and John W. Tukey
    - Average Life from Sudden Records, 1948 january 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Average Values of mean Squares in Factorials, 1956; 1 item; Cornfield, Jerome and John W Tukey
    - Bagplot: A Bivariate Boxplot, The, 1999 May 12; 1 item; Rousseeuw, Peter J., Ida Ruts and John W. Tukey
    - Basic Difficulty in the Patent vs. Publication Problem, A, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Basis for Discussion, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Beginning a Taxomony of Table, a Foreword for "The Gramatical Structure of Tables", 1987 August 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Better Coordinates for Combinations of Order Statistics, 1962 March 24; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Bias and Variance in Lower Slobovia, A Parable, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Bibliography of Ronald Aylmer Fisher, 1949 August 27; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Bidec t Table, A, n.d.; 1 item; Kafadar, Karen and John W. Tukey
    - Bio Essay I. The Metameter, 1949; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Bioassay I: The Metameter Problem, 1949 April; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Biometric View of the Problem of Diagnosis I, A, 1948 March 1; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Blank, 1977 March 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Book Review: "Industrial Experimentation" by K. A. Brownlee, 1946; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Book Review: "Multiple Factor Analysis" by L. L. Thurstone, 1947; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Book Review: "Probability for Statistical Methods" by F. N. David, 1949; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Book Review: "Sequential Analysis of Statistical Data: Applications" Prepared by the Satistical Research Group, Columbia University, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Book Review: "The Factorial Analysis of Human Ability, Second Edition" by Godfrey H. Thomson, 1947; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Book review: "Theory of Experimental Inference" by C. West Churchman, 1949; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Borrowing Strength in a Diversified Situtation, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Calculation of Allowances, The, 1992 January 7; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Can Least Squares Survive by Adopting a New Role, Special Note and Souvenir Sheets, 1973 April 28; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Can We Predict Where "Time Series" Should Go Next?, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Cancer Report, 1981; 2 items; Kafadar, Karen and John W. Tukey
    - Causation, Regression, and Path Analysis, 1954; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Chairman's Closure, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Chairmanship, 1968; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Checking the Shape of Discrete Distributions, 1985; 1 item; Hoaglin, David C. and John W. Tukey
    - Chemicals and Health, 1973 September; 1 item; Panel on Chemicals and Health of the President's Science Advisory Committee
    - Chlorofluoromethanes, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Choice and Change of Modes of Expression, The, 1960; Folder 1; Tukey, John W
    - Choice and Change of Modes of Expression, The, 1960; Folder 2; Tukey, John W
    - Choosing Techniques for the Analysis of Data, 1981 June 29; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Citation Index and the Information Problem, Opportunities and Research in Progress, 1962; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Citation Index for Statistics and Probability, A, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Citation Index for Statistics: an Introduction and a Progress Report, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Citation Index Release, 1964 December 22; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Citation Index: a Volume of the Index to Statistics and Probability, 1973; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Citation Index, 1973; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Class of Accumulation Patterns Useful in Support of Certain Agglomerative Clustering Algorithms, Internal Working Paper 89-10, 1989; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Closure in Lattices, 1941; 6 items; Birkhoff, Garrett and John W. Tukey
    - Code for Serials, A, 1969; 1 item; Dolby, J. l., H. L. Resnikoff, and John W. Tukey
    - Coding System for a Citation Index, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Cofinality in Ordered Systems, [1943]; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Cognistics Working Paper #1, 1981 May 20; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Cognostics Working Paper #2, 1981 June 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Cohort Analysis, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Collection of Points Relevant to Making Regression Incisive, A, 1990 September 17; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Collection of Points Relevant to Making Regression More Incisive, A, 1990 November 7; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Colloquium on Geostatistics, 1970; 3 item; Tukey, John W
    - Columns Divided into Bar and Their Competitors, 1989 July; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Combination of Results of Stated Precision: I. The Optimistic Case, 1982; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Combination of Results of Stated Precision: II. A More Realistic Case, 1984; 1 item; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Combinatorial, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Combining CL (confidence limits) and PL (partial limits) displays, 1990 May 21; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Combining Independent Results and Testing Their Significance, 1978 July 13; 1 item; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Comment on "More Intelligent Statistical Software and Statistical Expert Systems: Future Directions" by Gerald J. Hahn, 1985; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Comment on "Nonparametric Statistical Data Modeling" by Emanuel Parzen, 1979; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comment on Degrees of Freedom as Shares in a Sum of Squares, A, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comment, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments Made Before, Between, and After the Papers of the Third Session of the Computer Symposium, 21 June 1966, 1966 July 7; 1 comment; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on "Seasonality: Causation, Interpretation, and Implications" by Clive W.J. Granger, 1978; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on "Use of Spatial Analysis in Mineral Resource Evaluation" by F.P. Agterberg, 1984; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on "Use of Spatial Analysis in Mineral Resource Evaluation" by F.P. Agterberg, 1993; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on a Time Series Analysis by Anscombe, 1979 October 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on Control for the Pip with Trumpets and Bass Drums, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on Exploratory Data Analysis, 1970-1974; 22 items; Tukey, John W
      Includes correspondence
    - Comments on Iconolog Reduction of Angle Errors - Case, 1950; 2 items; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on Lange, Little and Taylor "Robust Statistical Modelling using the t-distribution" [84 JASA 881-896(89)], 1991 March 14; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on Multivariate Techniques, 1976; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on Path Coefficients and Related Topics, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on Predicting EPA's Forthcoming CO Standards in Light of New Clinical Evidence, 1991; 1 item; Sivak, Andrew and John W. Tukey
    - Comments on Random Balance, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comments on the Fitting of Power Series, 1973; 3 items; Beaton, Albert E. and John W. Tukey
    - Comments on the Philosophy that should underlie any Metropolitan Concepts and Statistics Projects, 1990 October 17; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Committee on the Uses of Computers Report, 1963; 4 items; Committee on the Uses of Computers
    - Compactness in General Spaces, 1940; 3 items; Tukey, John W
    - Comparing Empirical Distributions Over Time, 1987 September 8; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comparing Individual Means in the Analysis of Variance, 1949; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comparing Patterns by Analyses of Variance Techniques, 1991; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Comparing Two Small Samples on Many Items, 1954 February 8; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Complex Analyses of Variance with a Psychometric Example, n.d.; 1 item; Green, Bert F., Jr. and John W. Tukey
    - Complex Analyses of Variance: General Problems, 1958; 1 item; Green, Bert F., Jr. and John W. Tukey
    - Complex Analysis of Variance. II. The Analysis of Trends, 1 item; Green, Bert F., Jr. and John W. Tukey
    - Components in Regression, 1950; 5 items; Tukey, John W
    - Compromise Estimates for Location-like Situations, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Computerized Statistics: When Will We Have It?, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Computers in Undergraduate Education: Mathematics, Physics, Statistics, and Chemistry Report, 1967 December 8-9; 1 item; Statistics Panel
    - Computing and Using Rural versus Urban Measures in Statistical Applications, 1991; 1 item; Goodall, Colin R., Karen Kafadar and John W. Tukey
    - Computing Building Block, A, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Conclusions in Cooperation with Exploration, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Conclusions vs Decisions, 1955; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Conditional Monte Carlo for Normal Samples, Souvenir Sheets, 1954; 1 item; Trotter, Hale F. and John W. Tukey
    - Conference on the Discontinuance of Nuclear Weapons Tests Report, 1959 December 18; 3 items; Technical Working Group 2
    - Confidence Limits for Parabola Vertices and Hence for Symmetrical Minima and Maxima, 1949 July 22; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Confidence Procedures are Better, Souvenir Sheets, 1954 March 8; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Configural Polysampling, a Route to Practical Robustness, 1989; 1 item; Cohen, M., G. Easton, Krystinik K. Bell, F. O'Brian, S. Morgenthaler, and John W. Tukey
    - Configural Polysampling, 1987 September 25; 1 item; Morganthaler, Stephen and John W. Tukey
    - Consolidating Contour Maps, 1991 May 3; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Consumer Datesware, 1989; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Control and Stash Philosophy for Two-handed, Flexible, and Immediate Control of a Graphic Display, 1982 February 4; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Control Environment and Stash Philosophy for Data-View-Modification Computer Graphics, 1981 November 10; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Control of Calibration of Nearly Linear Devices, The, 1944 May 31; 4 items; Tukey, John W
    - Control Philosophy for Two-handed Flexible, and Immediate Control of a Graphic Display, 1981 May; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Control-Charting Automated Laboratory Instruments when many Successive Differences may be Zero, 1989; 1 item; Ciminera, Joseph L. and John W. Tukey
    - Controlling Error in Multiple Comparisons, with Special Attention to the National Assessment of Educational Progress, 1994 December; 1 item; Jones, Lyle V., John W. Tukey, and Valerie S.L. Williams
    - Convergence and Uniformity in Topology, 1940; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Corner Test for Association, A, 1947 December; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Correction to "A Note on Linear Functionals," A, 1938; 1 item; Boas, Ralph P. and John W. Tukey
    - Correlation Bias in the Presence of Stratum Heterogeneity, n.d; 1 item; Kadane, Joseph B., Michael Meyer, and John W. Tukey
    - Correlation of Ranges of Correlated Deviates, 1966; 1 item; Kurtz, T. E., R. F. Link, John W. Tukey, and D. L. Wallace
    - Cost of Inappropriate Weighting in Least-Square Fitting, The, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - CPS Program to do Two Way Median Analysis for PPS, A, 1974 April 12; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Criticism of Transformations, The, [1954]; 7 items; Anscombe, Francis J., and John W. Tukey
    - Curly Contrails in the Snow!, 1981 September 25; Pt. 1 and II; Tukey, John W
    - Curves as Parameters, and Touch Estimation, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis and Behavioral Science Or Learning to Bear the Quantitative Man's Burden by Shunning Badmandments, 1960; Folder 1; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis and Behavioral Science Or Learning to Bear the Quantitative Man's Burden by Shunning Badmandments, 1960; Folder 2; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis and Behavioral Science Or Learning to Bear the Quantitative Man's Burden by Shunning Badmandments, 1960; Folder 3; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis and Data Display in the Context of Many Sensors, I. Iconization, Summarization, and Available Schemata, 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis and Regression, A Second Course in Statistics, 1976 March 4; 1 item; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Data Analysis and Regression, A Second Course in Statistics, 1976; box 1; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Data Analysis and Regression, A Second Course in Statistics, 1976; box 2; Mosteller, Frederick and John W. Tukey
    - Data Analysis and Statistics: A Tutorial Overview, 1 item; Tukey, John W. and Martin B. Wilk
    - Data Analysis and Statistics: an Expository Overview, 1 item; Tukey, John W. and Martin B. Wilk
    - Data Analysis and Statistics: Principles and Practice, 1 item; Tukey, John W. and Martin B. Wilk
    - Data Analysis and Statistics: Techniques and Approaches, 1965 November 1-3; 1 item; Tukey, John W. and Martin B. Wilk
    - Data Analysis and the Frontiers of Geophysics, 1964; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis for Molecular Structure: Today and Tomorrow, 1991; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis, 1995-2005, 1993 April 2; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis, Computation and Mathematics, 1972 April; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis, Including Statistics, 1965 July 4; 1 item; Frederick Mosteller and John W. Tukey
    - Data Analysis: History and Prospects, 1984; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analysis, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analyst's Comments on a Variety of Points and Issues, A, 1978 March 13; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data Analytic Approach to Plant Breeding Trials, A, n.d.; Folder 1; Basford, Kay E. and John W. Tukey
    - Data Analytic Approach to Plant Breeding Trials, A, n.d.; Folder 2; Basford, Kay E. and John W. Tukey
    - Data Screen, n.d.; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data-Based Graphics: Visual Display in the Decades to Come, 1990; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Data-Driven View Selection; Agglomeration and Sharpening, 1 item; Tukey, Paul A., and John W. Tukey
    - Definite and Potential Additions to the NS (=Atopical = Non-Sig = Stop) List from a First Examination of a Plot Perm Section, 1985; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Demographic Data Analysis Using an Interactive Computer, 1974 July; 1 item; McNeil, D. R. and John W. Tukey
    - Denominatorless and Other Modified Chi-Squares: an Investigation into Comparative Properties of Constituents, 1979 October 29; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Deriving Appropriate Standard for Census Undercount Adjustment, 1986 March 23-26; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Describing Distributions by a Few Points, or by an Ellipse, Using Moment Matching, 1991 February 5; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Design and Analysis of Experiments and More Realistic Techniques for Data Analysis, 1986 March 18; 1 item; Tukey, John W
    - Designing Graphics for Impact, 1987 July 30; 1 item; Tukey, John W